question_data = [{"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "French is an official language in Canada.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The Sun rises from the North.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "On average, at least 1 person is killed by a drunk driver in the United States every hour.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Pluto is a planet.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Adolf Hitler was born in Australia. ", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {
    "category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The Lego Group was founded in 1932.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Jingle Bells was originally meant for Thanksgiving", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Ping-Pong originated in England", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
